

ARMANDO ZINCKE

PROGRAMMER

843.592.8619



armando.zincke@gmail.com 🎻



linkedin.com/in/mando



github.com/Manduco %

Goal-oriented, efficient, and resourceful Web Developer and Marine Corps Veteran with a decade of IT experience and a passion to solve problems through explorative code. Creative and highly selfmotivated team player that possesses an affinity for technology and customer-centric design with strong programming and scripting skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Practically Pocus LLC | Gainesville, Florida | January 2020 - Present

Technical Analyst

- Identify and implement system modifications to improve efficiency and reduce cost of operations
- Determine appropriate procedures for all IT technologies and assist in all equipment configurations
- Manage, configure, and administer more than 150 desktops, laptops, tablets and smart phones
- Establish and manage E-mailing firewall to include filtering and redirection for optimal security

OPIE Software | Gainesville, Florida | March 2019 – January 2020

IT Analyst

- Engaged vendor to install and implement a new faxing system while training 35+ clients and employees
- Maximized equipment readiness by implementing a customized factory image for new hires with Dell
- Implemented e-mail phishing training and DNS security testing to achieve 94% on security score card
- Crafted monthly reports to track e-faxing and Dell system usage, leveraging BASH scripts and SQL queries
- Developed PowerShell and Python scripts to standardize all e-mail signatures, automate domain joins, silent software installs, and remote server logs

Santa Fe College | Gainesville, Florida | May 2018 – March 2019

Lab Tutor, Information Technology Education (ITE)Department

- Tutored 40+ students in various computer programming courses from Databases, Object-Orientated programming and web applications, including SQL and database creation, C++, C#, Java, and jQuery
- Conducted quarterly equipment refreshers, software installs, and hardware fixes to maintain integrity and security of all labs and equipment in a Windows and Mac environment

United States Marine Corps | Beaufort, South Carolina | Okinawa, Japan | September 2011 – September 2015 IT Administrative Specialist (MOS-0111)

- Handled administrative and managerial tasks by managing databases, completing leave authorizations, and issuing identification cards to more than 750 Active Duty members and visitors
- Preparation and maintained command punishments, naval correspondence, travel orders, and directives

EDUCATION

Santa Fe College | Gainesville, Florida | 2021

Bachelor of Science in Information Systems Technology – Programming Emphasis 115 Credits Earned

Santa Fe College | Gainesville, Florida | 2020

Associate of Science in Programming and Analysis

Miami Dade College | Miami, Florida | 2016 Associate Pathway in Computer Engineering

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming/Scripting: Python, PowerShell, BASH, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, SQL, HTML5 & CSS3
- Industry: Project Management, Server Management, Active Directory
- Software: Installation. Debugging, Microsoft suite, WordPress, Hyper-V, JIRA, Confluence
- OS: Windows, Exchange Server, Ubuntu, MacOS/iOS
- Network: Configurations, Servers, Routers, TCP/IP, DNS, IIS, Firewall and VoIP